hentaiweeb.com 2016-12-03

# Hentai Weeb Privacy Policy

### What information does Hentai Weeb collect?

Hentai Weeb and its staff will not ask for, and does not collect any data from its users. The comment system, powered by Disqus, requires registration information to be supplied, however, Hentai Weeb itself does not require any information from users visiting the website.

Protecting our users’ privacy is of utmost importance to us.

### Video Disclaimer

Hentai Weeb does not host any video content on its servers. All video content is obtained through, and embedded through external video hosting services, such as, but not limited to, Yourupload, Dailymotion, Mp4Upload, Stream, Openload and more.

### Copyright Infringement

In the case of copyright infringement, we ask that you instead contact the responsible parties, i.e., the video hosts actually hosting the videos. Hentai Weeb simply embeds videos that already exist on other websites, in principle, conducting business in the same manner as Google, or any online search engine.

Hentai Weeb, however, believes in enforcing Hentai rights holders’ intellectual property, and as such, have no problem complying with _valid DMCA requests_. Please make sure to send them directly to our DMCA-related email.

Hentai Weeb does not accept responsibility for any content uploaded off of its servers.

### Does Hentai Weeb use cookies?

As most websites on the internet, yes. For those of you who are unaware, cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser ( _if you allow cookies, that is_ ) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Hentai Weeb uses cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregated data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools for users in the future.

### Advertising

Hentai Weeb uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may compile data (not including any personal information) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you have any queries regarding the purchase of advertising space, or problems with current advertising, then please feel free to contact us at our advertising-related email.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Your Consent

By using [HentaiWeeb.com](http://hentaiweeb.com/), you fully consent to our Privacy Policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

In the future, Hentai Weeb reserves the right to make any changes to our Privacy Policy, at any time.
